allprodad.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Family First : Family First

### FAMILY FIRST PRIVACY

Family First places a high priority on protecting the privacy of our donors, email subscribers, event attendees and website users across all of our programs and sites. This Family First Privacy Policy applies to each of our programs and sites:Family First, All Pro Dad, iMOM and Family Minute.

### WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

Family First donors, subscribers and event attendees voluntarily provide us with contact information (such as name, e-mail address, zip code, etc.). We may use this information for specific, limited purposes. You may always opt out, either now or at any time in the future, if you do not wish to continue receiving our communications.

### ONLINE INFORMATION

We may collect information about the online services that you use and how you use them, including when you visit different parts of our site or selections you make regarding our services or resources. We may also automatically collect certain technical information including: Device-Specific information, such as hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile information (if you use a mobile device to access the site); and Access and Server Log information, such as your navigation paths and search queries, internet protocol (IP) address, device event information such as crashes and system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, date and time of your request, referral URL, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser type, mobile device, account, operating system, and other technical information.

### HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

Family First uses your personal information to provide you with personalized service, to send e-mails to you regarding our services or important updates, to answer your requests, etc. You may choose to opt out at any time, from some or all communications from us. We may also use your information to track visitors to our websites. This allows us to evaluate the popularity of certain pages and tools so that we can better serve our followers. It also allows us to provide aggregate data about our followers (not identifying individuals, but showing how many users visited which pages, for example) to outside parties. Your personally identifiable information is never disclosed to third parties without your consent. Please keep in mind that comments sections, discussion forums, and other similar areas of our services are public. Any information posted in those areas is viewable and usable by anyone that has access to the site.

### EMAIL PRIVACY

Family First does not provide, sell, or rent email addresses or other personal information to anyone outside our organization.

### EXTERNAL LINKS

Family First emails, communications and websites may include links to external websites. These links do not fall under Family First’s control, and Family First is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of external websites or organizations. Your use of any links is solely at your own risk.

### OTHER IMPORTANT PRIVACY CONSIDERATIONS

Our site is not intended for the independent use of children, and we will not knowingly collect information for any child under the age of thirteen. If you are the parent of a child and have a concern regarding your child’s information on our site, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Our website and associated services are hosted in the United States. Even if you are outside the United States, your information will be processed and stored in the United States, and you are consenting to such processing and storage.

### MODIFICATIONS

Family First retains the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting an updated policy on our website(s). Your continued use of our websites and tools after the date of any such update will be deemed to be your agreement to the current policy terms.
